<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Topic 1 on it&#39;s my life</title>
    <link>http://www.example.com/topics/topic-1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Topic 1 on it&#39;s my life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <copyright>© 2011~2016 kiersonal ♪ Powered by Jekyll.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 23:14:40 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.example.com/topics/topic-1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 23:14:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, I know it&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to introduce myself if I&amp;rsquo;m willing to be a big mouth!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned in sidebar, this is a totally independent blog that Stand Alone with my real life. I&amp;rsquo;ve been spent nearly two months to publish this blog, without losing any functions I want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is kiersonal. also, a Stand Alone name seperate with all of my social media, although I no longer use them anymore, Software Engineering was my major, and that&amp;rsquo;s why I so pursue such a product my own and why I&amp;rsquo;m a little bit geek.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to great Internet, i could found some help on the websites below, which is also what i want to thanks!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/extras/datafiles&#34;&gt;https://gohugo.io/extras/datafiles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.pyco.me/hugo-static-site-generator/&#34;&gt;http://www.pyco.me/hugo-static-site-generator/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://themes.gohugo.io/hyde-y/&#34;&gt;http://themes.gohugo.io/hyde-y/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://azeril.me/&#34;&gt;http://azeril.me/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://blog.coderzh.com/&#34;&gt;http://blog.coderzh.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, i have to acknowledged that, excuses lasts almost two months, and I just create this blog within one day&amp;hellip;..&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;ll Be Seeing A New &#39;Predator&#39; Movie Coming In March 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/2016/02/29/well-be-seeing-a-new-predator-movie-coming-in-march-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 21:55:36 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/2016/02/29/well-be-seeing-a-new-predator-movie-coming-in-march-2018/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://images.techtimes.com/data/images/full/213440/the-predator.jpg?w=600&#34; /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;No one saw the teaser poster for the new &amp;laquo;Predator&amp;raquo; film coming but, when it did show up in its Facebook account on Feb. 15; fans knew that it was only a matter of time before the nearly invisible creatures would make reappearance in our nightmares once again. To be more specific, 20th Century Fox announced that the highly advance alien race would be swooping in cinemas in two years&amp;rsquo; time on March 2, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that we know what is coming for the science fiction loving human race, we at least have a chance to prepare ourselves for an action-packed- and quite possibly, gore-filled- encounter with predators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, we&amp;rsquo;re not talking about any other predator you have seen because Shane Black, one of the supporting actors in the original 1987 Arnold Schwarzenegger led &amp;laquo;Predator&amp;raquo; film, who is serving as the Director and co-writer with Fred Dekker, promises an inventive sequel about &amp;laquo;The Predator.&amp;raquo; You read that correctly, it&amp;rsquo;s not any predator but the predator, though what exactly that means eludes us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, what we know for sure is that Black and Dekker will not just be focusing on pulling information that we already know from the previous &amp;laquo;Predator&amp;raquo; films and its spin-offs but that the co-writers have actually mined the rich mythology of the alien race and that we should actually prepare to know more about them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;laquo;I think it&amp;rsquo;s genius and I think it&amp;rsquo;s entertaining, and what it did is recreate a famous franchise in a different, interesting way; looking at it from a different light [&amp;hellip;] you&amp;rsquo;re going to get something you don&amp;rsquo;t expect and you&amp;rsquo;re going to say, &amp;lsquo;This is the most entertaining way to reinvent a franchise,&amp;raquo; John Davis said of Black and Dekker&amp;rsquo;s script. Davis will serve as a producer for &amp;laquo;The Predator.&amp;raquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;laquo;The Predator&amp;raquo; seems to be promising and, with how its mythos was treated in the sequels and spin-offs, we can only think positively about the new addition.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>谐星语录之粗糙的英格兰</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/2016/02/29/%E8%B0%90%E6%98%9F%E8%AF%AD%E5%BD%95%E4%B9%8B%E7%B2%97%E7%B3%99%E7%9A%84%E8%8B%B1%E6%A0%BC%E5%85%B0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 21:41:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/2016/02/29/%E8%B0%90%E6%98%9F%E8%AF%AD%E5%BD%95%E4%B9%8B%E7%B2%97%E7%B3%99%E7%9A%84%E8%8B%B1%E6%A0%BC%E5%85%B0/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=raKA5USbw7c&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=raKA5USbw7c&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;关于足球的吐槽&#34;&gt;关于足球的吐槽~~&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;果然是毒奶&#34;&gt;果然是毒奶&lt;/h3&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; padding-top: 30px; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/raKA5USbw7c&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%;&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>谈谈创建该博客的事</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/2016/01/30/%E8%B0%88%E8%B0%88%E5%88%9B%E5%BB%BA%E8%AF%A5%E5%8D%9A%E5%AE%A2%E7%9A%84%E4%BA%8B/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 21:53:51 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/2016/01/30/%E8%B0%88%E8%B0%88%E5%88%9B%E5%BB%BA%E8%AF%A5%E5%8D%9A%E5%AE%A2%E7%9A%84%E4%BA%8B/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;怎么说呢，其实有这个想法是很早之前就有的了，想着说自己也该写点东西，去记录自己的成长，回首往日的自己，反省。但毕竟只是想想，睡一觉也就忘记了。而在今年年初，关闭了朋友圈，不再刷新社交软件。我把这个当作一种成长吧。无处分享自己的想法，是一种煎熬……于是，就在网上疯狂地寻找着如何创建博客的资料。自己就想着，弄个博客也算是对自己的宽恕吧！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;先是在知乎发有很多人都在用现Github————这个真要吐槽自己了，N早之前就注册，却并没怎么用(◎﹏◎)————搭建属于自己的博客，但是方法太多，在写这篇文章的前几天，我用的是Hexo，可是不知道是自己太笨还是怎么，按着教程走，发现很多博主虽然写得详细，却经常忽略一些极小的细节，导致自己对Hexo失去了信心。这篇博文事实上是用了Hugo这么一个极大简化配置过程的小工具来完成的。在此，也非常感谢Hugo！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;现在已是美国PST（太平洋标准时间）晚上十一点多了，在两个小时之前，我才知道自己的农历生日是我在美国的星期天（农历二十三）&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;这段时间自己为了弄个博客基本上弄到晚上很晚，并不是想说自己有多么努力，因为毕竟是自己喜欢的啊，是自己愿意去做的啊！这是天注定？在完成一个简陋的框架之后，妈妈跟我说明天是我的生日。但是自己对生日的概念已经模糊了，感觉没什么值得纪念的。从来没有想过，这个最为特殊的生日，我送给了自己最好的礼物——这个blog。也许简陋到爆，大家看到的那些乱七八糟的文章其实还在测试——也许过段时间我会把它们删了；还不知道怎么发图，发链接，评论。不过没关系，不需要向大家承诺，我自己会在日后一点点地更新。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;结语&#34;&gt;结语：&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;想起了在来到西雅图之后的第二天，写过这么一句话：把自己打成狗，重新做人！今天，这个孩子已经四个月大，我会把他抚养成一名优秀的人的！&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>