<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scifi on it&#39;s my life</title>
    <link>http://www.example.com/tags/scifi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scifi on it&#39;s my life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <copyright>© 2011~2016 kiersonal ♪ Powered by Jekyll.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 21:55:36 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://www.example.com/tags/scifi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;ll Be Seeing A New &#39;Predator&#39; Movie Coming In March 2018</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/2016/02/29/well-be-seeing-a-new-predator-movie-coming-in-march-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 21:55:36 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/2016/02/29/well-be-seeing-a-new-predator-movie-coming-in-march-2018/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://images.techtimes.com/data/images/full/213440/the-predator.jpg?w=600&#34; /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;No one saw the teaser poster for the new &amp;laquo;Predator&amp;raquo; film coming but, when it did show up in its Facebook account on Feb. 15; fans knew that it was only a matter of time before the nearly invisible creatures would make reappearance in our nightmares once again. To be more specific, 20th Century Fox announced that the highly advance alien race would be swooping in cinemas in two years&amp;rsquo; time on March 2, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that we know what is coming for the science fiction loving human race, we at least have a chance to prepare ourselves for an action-packed- and quite possibly, gore-filled- encounter with predators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No, we&amp;rsquo;re not talking about any other predator you have seen because Shane Black, one of the supporting actors in the original 1987 Arnold Schwarzenegger led &amp;laquo;Predator&amp;raquo; film, who is serving as the Director and co-writer with Fred Dekker, promises an inventive sequel about &amp;laquo;The Predator.&amp;raquo; You read that correctly, it&amp;rsquo;s not any predator but the predator, though what exactly that means eludes us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, what we know for sure is that Black and Dekker will not just be focusing on pulling information that we already know from the previous &amp;laquo;Predator&amp;raquo; films and its spin-offs but that the co-writers have actually mined the rich mythology of the alien race and that we should actually prepare to know more about them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;laquo;I think it&amp;rsquo;s genius and I think it&amp;rsquo;s entertaining, and what it did is recreate a famous franchise in a different, interesting way; looking at it from a different light [&amp;hellip;] you&amp;rsquo;re going to get something you don&amp;rsquo;t expect and you&amp;rsquo;re going to say, &amp;lsquo;This is the most entertaining way to reinvent a franchise,&amp;raquo; John Davis said of Black and Dekker&amp;rsquo;s script. Davis will serve as a producer for &amp;laquo;The Predator.&amp;raquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;laquo;The Predator&amp;raquo; seems to be promising and, with how its mythos was treated in the sequels and spin-offs, we can only think positively about the new addition.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>